# Mukhammadzhon Khakimov

## Frontend Developer

Last update: December 4, 2022

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

1 https://Muhammadzhon.github.io/muhammad-bio

Residence	♠ Osh, Kyrgyzstan
Linkedin	in <u>Mukhammadzhon</u>
GitHub	Muhammadzhon
Phone	+996 (555) 00 43 45
Email	<u>hmuhammadjon</u>

HTML CSS SPA Github JavaScript React English Turkish Russian

I'm a frontend developer. The purpose of my last 5 years happened to find the job which I love. And I realized only web development was going to fill my path of life! Studied HTML, CSS and JavaScript, now I'm learning React and It makes me confident and ambitious.

## **Professional Experience**

10/2022 - Current

#### Trainee

Bi-Soft Ltd takes leading position in Kyrgyzstan market.

As a Trainee my task is:

- \* Analyze the code structure
- \* Maintain software specifications
- \* Work closely with other developers
- \* Accomplish tasks which was given by teamlead
- \* Write clear and consistent code

Good knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and Git Strong communication skills Well organized team player

11/2022 - present

### Way of Samurai project

Way of Samurai is a replica of social media paltform

As a lerner I'm:

- \* Studying framework React
- \* Practicing HTML, CSS and JS
- \* Writing code on VS Code editor
- \* Learning to devide into components
- \* Building the structure from scratches

### Education

Ahmet Yesevi International Kazak-Turkish University [2011 - 2016]